The condition of the patient of bed no. 13 is still unstable.
‫حالة السرير رقم 13 غير مستقرة
Add some radix adenophorae
أضف
in his medicine.
في دواءه
Did you see that?
هل رأيت
Balance.
‫قفي ثابتة‬
My waist strength...
خصري
I can practice dancing now.
يمكنني التدرب على الرقص
You'd better do your best as an intern
من الأفضل أن تكوني متدربة جيدة
and focus on drawing.
أرسم بشكل جيد
Are you jealous of me?
تحسدني؟
Hey.
مهلاً.
I haven't finished yet.
لم أنتهي بعد
Take down some notes for bed no. 18.
تذكر السرير رقم 18
Ouyang, did you really buy the lamb meat?
‫أو يانغ هل حقا ذهبت لشراء لحم الضأن
My friend suddenly asked me to meet her.
تم استدعائي من قبل صديقي
I'm sorry.
آسف
Why don't you try it yourself first?
ما رأيك أن تتذوقها بنفسك اليوم
Okay.
حسنا حسنا
Bye.
مع السلامة
He's such a smarty-pant.
هذا ذكي جدا
Orange.
البرتقال
Ouyang Yu is so nice to you.
أويانغ يو يعاملك بشكل جيد
Of course.
بالطبع
After all,
بعد كل شيء
we've been through hardships together.
أنا وهو أخوان
Then how is he
هو
compared to Mr. Xiao?
مقارنة بالمعلم شياو؟
Can they...
إنهما
be compared?
ما المقارنة بينهما
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
You scared me.
لقد أخفتني
Why are you free to pick us up
لماذا لديك وقت لاستقبالنا اليوم
from the hospital to have a meal today?
لتناول الطعام من المستشفى
I came here for a purpose.
أتيت إلى هنا من أجل الغرض
There's a gift.
لدي هدية.
I'm here to ask you
أنا هنا لأسألكم
for some ideas on
أطلب منكم مساعدتي
what I should wear
ما هي الملابس التي سترتديها
to meet my goddess.
أفضل
In my opinion,
في رأيي
you should save some money.
لا داعي لذلك
Your goddess is very experienced.
إن ملكتك هي أيضًا شخص يعرف العالم
Since she decided to see you,
بما أنها قررت رؤيتك
she must have given up
فلا بد أنها استسلمت
her pursuit of a glamorous appearance.
السعي وراء هذا السطح
I think
أعتقد
the key is simplicity.
أن الطريق البسيط
Hey.
مهلاً
Recently, in order to
من أجل الجسم مؤخراً
maintain my physique,
للحفاظ على هذه القامة
I haven't had a meal at all.
لم أتناول وجبة واحدة
I suggest the black and white outfit.
هل هو أسود وأبيض
It's suitable for all occasions.
كل مكان مناسب
It looks very formal too.
ويبدو رسميًا جدًا
Look at her.
انظر إليها
You should learn from Xiaoxiao, okay?
عليك أن تتعلم من شياو شياو
I admire her
أنا معجب بها
sense of propriety.
إحساس الحد
Have you ordered?
هل طلبت الطعام؟
We were waiting for you.
أنتظرك
What?
ماذا؟
Hello, may I take your order now?
مرحبا هل يمكنني طلب الطعام الآن
Look at your low level of courage.
انظروا إلى شجاعتكم
I've eaten.
لقد أكلت
Didn't you
لقد
just say you haven't eaten yet?
ألم تقل أنك لم تأكل
I'm on a diet right now.
ألم تخفض الوزن مؤخرًا؟
A diet.
تخفيف الوزن
You're back, Dr. Song.
لقد عدت أيها الطبيب سونغ
You're waiting to embarrass me in public?
أنت تنتظر معاقبتي علنية هنا
Oh, right.
بالمناسبة
How was the lamb in the third canteen?
ماذا عن لحم الضأن في المطعم الثالث؟
Quite good, right?
ليس سيئا
Not too bad,
لا بأس به
because someone wasn't there.
بعض الناس غير موجودون
Come on.
أنت حقًا
I've been studying fabric art recently.
كنت أدرس القماش مؤخرًا
I made a sachet for you.
صنعت كيسًا عطرًا لك
It's such a cute persimmon.
يا لها من طاقة لطيفة
This is
هذا
a small Orange.
البرتقال الصغير
Really?
حقا
By the way, you're really hardworking,
أنت مجعد جدا
you even know how to embroider.
يمكنك حتى التطريز
Not bad.
لا بأس به
After all, I'm an artist.
بعد كل شيء فنان
By the way,
بالمناسبة
is it really
إنه حقا
not a persimmon?
أليست بذور؟
Dr. Xiao,
الطبيب شياو
I don't know much about this dispensing ratio.
أنا لا أفهم هذا المطابقة
Can you explain it to me?
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني
Did you pass on my message
طلبت منك أن تخبر الممرضة
to the Head Nurse?
هل ذهبت
I'll be right there.
سأذهب على الفور
I'll clean this up when I'm back.
سأرتب بعد عودتي
Dating is not easy.
ليس من السهل الوقوع في الحب
You need to know how to make handicrafts.
يجب أن تعرف كيفية صناعة يدوية صغيرة
Fireworks.
الألعاب النارية
Girl.
فتاة
Confession.
اعترف
Such beautiful and lonely words.
هذه الكلمات الجميلة والوحيدة
[The Mortal World of Love]
متصلة
what kind of romantic scenario will it be?
‫كيف سيكون المشهد الرومانسي‬
Just thinking about it is fun.
هذا ممتع
Dr. Xiao,
الطبيب شياو
Dr. Song said I need to add radix adenophorae for bed no. 18.
قال الطبيب شياو سونغ أن السرير الثامن عشر أضف الجنسنغ الجنوبي
How much dosage?
كم عدد الجرعة
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك
Where did he go?
أين ذهبت؟
When did he start playing with toys?
متى تلعب لعبة
The Mortal World of Love?
عالم الحب
Bocui Fireworks Festival?
عيد الألعاب النارية باي تسوي
So he likes fireworks.
اتضح أنه يحب الألعاب النارية
Are you done?
هل انتهيت؟
Yes.
نعم
How is it?
ما رأيك؟
Not bad, right?
ليس سيئا
I've always been a supporter of master painter Song.
أنا دائماً من يدعم رسامة سونغ
That's right.
هذا صحيح
Hey, do you want have dinner with Wei
تناولي العشاء مع الأخت وي
together?
لنذهب
No.
لا
I just came back.
لقد عدت للتو
Dr. Sun asked me to get familiar with
طلب مني الدكتورة سون أن أعرف
the cases in our hospital.
حالة مستشفانا
You're all so hardworking.
‫سأموت
A smile brings spring warmth.
ابتسامة في الربيع
Smile.
ابتسمي
Wei.
الأخت وي
Orange.
البرتقال
Have a seat.
اجلس
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
What can I do for you?
ما الأمر؟
Go ahead.
تفضل
I...
أنا
want to confess my feelings to someone.
أريد أن أعترف بحبي لشخص ما
So,
لذلك
I have to choose a place
يجب أن نختار مكانًا
but he hasn't replied yet.
لكنه لم يرد علي بعد
Let me see.
دعني أرى
What?
ماذا؟
Recall it immediately.
اسحبها بسرعة
Are you done?
انسحبوا أم لا انسحبوا أم لا
Recalled?
انسحبوا
How could you reveal it to him in advance?
كيف يمكنك تسريحه مسبقاً؟
If you spoil it, it won't be exciting.
إذا قمت بتفضيحه لن يكون هناك أي أفكار جديدة
Let me see.
دعني أرى
Which restaurant did you choose?
ما المطعم الذي اخترته؟
I've to choose a restaurant?
تريد اختيار المطعم
What else?
وإلا
I'm thinking
أنا أفكر
whether I should go to this house
أن أذهب إلى هذا المنزل
or my vacation villa
أو إلى فيلا عطلتي
or the villa in the hills...
أو ذلك الدار
Or...
أو
I haven't decided yet.
لم أقرر بعد
Just now,
قبل قليل
I was narrow-minded.
أنا ضيق
Narrow-minded.
ضيق
Do you have
ماذا لديك
any ideas?
فكرتك؟
I'm thinking
أنا أفكر
if I choose this place,
إذا اخترت هنا
I'll rent some drones and use them to
سأغلق طائرة بدون طيار
spell out words in the sky.
‫وأجمع كلمة أخرى‬
If I choose this place,
إذا اخترت هنا
I'll prepare
سأعد
a candlelight dinner on the lake.
عشاء ضوء الشموع على الماء
Then I'll set off fireworks.
ثم سأطلق الألعاب النارية
What do you think?
ما رأيك؟
Bocui Fireworks Festival?
عيد الألعاب النارية باي تسوي
Who says guys don't like romance?
من قال أن الرجال لا يحبون الرومانسية
They just like
هم فقط يحبون
bigger flowers.
زهور أكبر
So,
لذلك
setting off fireworks
الألعاب النارية
is the best choice.
هو أفضل خيار
You also think this is good?
هل تعتقد أن هذا جيد أيضًا؟
Yes.
نعم
I'll pick you up at the hospital tomorrow
سآتي إلى المستشفى لأخذك غداً
and you help me set up the place.
ثم ساعدني في ترتيب الموقع
No problem.
لا مشكلة
It's decided. Cheers.
هذا هو القرار   في صحتك
Okay.
حسنا
One is controlled at 23 to 25 degrees
أحدهما يسيطر على 23 إلى 25 درجة
and the other is at 25 to 28 degrees.
أحدهما يتحكم في 25 إلى 28 درجة
Don't worry, Professor Song.
اطمئن يا أستاذ سونغ
Dr. Xiao.
دكتورة شياو
You're still here?
لم تعودي بعد
Why are you back?
لماذا عدت
I was going home,
لقد عدت إلى المنزل
but I forgot to bring the rent renewal contract back.
اكتشفت أن العقد المستمرة نسيت أن آخذه
I have to bring it back to the landlord.
يجب إرسالها إلى المالك
I'll talk to you later.
لن أتحدث معك الآن
I'm leaving.
سأذهب الآن
Okay.
نعم
Was that her?
هل كانت هي؟
Wei, you can count on me.
يا الأخت وي اتركي هذا الأمر لي
I’m an expert
أنا
in this.
في هذا
Okay?
حسنا
Morning, Orange.
صباح الخير البرتقال
Morning.
صباح الخير
How is it? Are you busy today?
كيف حالك هل أنت مشغول اليوم
I'm busy tonight.
أنا مشغولة الليلة
I brought you something good today.
لقد أحضرت لك شيء جيد اليوم
What is it?
ما هذا الشيء الجيد
So mysterious.
غامض جدا
You'll definitely need it today.
يجب أن تستخدمه اليوم
Underhanded trick.
خدعة صغيرة
This...
هذا هذا
It's...
إنه
a perfume sachet pendant?
عبارة عن كيس العطر
Yes.
نعم نعم
A pendant for the sachet.
قلادة على الكيس
You hang it to the sachet.
من أجل تعليق الكيس
You made an entire set.
هذا المكان كامل
It's quite good.
لكن لا حاجة لإرسال القليل كل يوم
Thank you.
شكرا
Sit down.
اجلس
On the table.
على الطاولة
Yes.
نعم
I said
قلت في ذلك الوقت
you will need it today.
أنك ستحتاج اليوم
There's no mistake.
صحيح
Why is it gone?
كيف لا يوجد
Orange.
البرتقال
Actually, that gift. I...
في الواقع تلك الهدية أنا
I...
أنا
I know, I understand.
فهمت، أعرف كل شيء
-Wei. -Orange.
‫الأخت وي البرتقال‬
Ouyang Yu.
‫أو يانغ يوي‬
Hello.
مرحبا
Why are you here?
لماذا أتيت إلى المستشفى أيضا
I'm here to recuperate.
جئت إلى المستشفى للتعافي
Are you going out together?
ماذا؟ هل ستخرجين؟
I'm going to confess my feelings
أريد أن أعترف بحبي
and Orange is helping me set up the place.
‫ساعدني في ترتيب البرتقال
Confess your feelings?
اعترف بحبها
Then I'll help too.
دعني أساعدك
I'll give support to your romance.
من الجيد أن نساعد الحب
Okay?
ممكن
Get in.
اركبي السيارة
With more people, we can work faster.
المزيد من العمال وفر دقيقة واحدة
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
The VIP patient left the hospital without permission.
خرج المريض VIP من المستشفى بدون إذن
I have to make sure he's safe.
يجب أن أضمن سلامته
Your appearance is much scarier.
أنت تظهر هكذا أكثر رعبا
Let's not talk about unrelated stuff.
دعنا نتوقف عن الحديث
-Go! -Let's go.
هيا بنا
For this...
هذا
you should measure the distance.
‫قم بالترتيب‬
Make sure they're the same distance apart.
‫كل واحد متساوي تمامًا‬
No, no.
لا لا
You should...
‫خذ هذا‬
move it more to the front.
اخرج
Ouyang Yu,
‫أو يانغ يو
how do you open that sculpture?
كيف فتحت تلك النحت
I want to put my wrist watch inside.
أريد وضع ساعةي في الداخل
Wait, let me take a look.
‫انتظر دعني ألقي نظرة‬
It's... almost done.
تقريبا
I think it's almost done here too.
أعتقد أن هذا الجانب تقريبا
Let's go to the lake
لنذهب إلى البحيرة
and decorate it.
للترتيب
Let's go.
هيا
Look.
انظر
I pulled this hand
‫لقد تحركت هذه اليد‬
and moved the crown.
لقد تحركت هذا البطن
I even rotated this ball.
حتى هذه الكرة
But I can't open it.
لا يمكنني فتحها
I'm going to find Orange.
سأذهب للبحث عن البرتقال
So stupid.
غبي جدا
Hey.
ألو
What are you doing here?
لماذا أنت هنا
What are you wearing?
ماذا ترتدين
I...
أنا
Can't I come?
ألا يمكنك القدوم؟
We need to prepare more cakes.
يجب إعداد هذه الكعكات أكثر
She likes them. You should bring them to her later.
هذه الأخت الكبيرة تحب تناولها بعد قليل أرسلها لها
Okay.
حسنًا
Take this to Hall 1 later.
أرسل هذا إلى غرفة رقم 1 بعد قليل
And the wine glass. Make it cleaner.
‫وهناك كأس النبيذ  نظف قليلا
That's all.
هكذا
Orange asked you to help out, right?
هل طلبت منك البرتقال العمل
What are you performing?
‫ماذا تلعب
Acrobatics.
المهارات البسيطة
Am I funny?
هل أنا مضحك
Why is Orange here?
‫لماذا تأتي البرتقال
She doesn't know Drizzle.
‫لا تعرف شي يو كبيرة أيضا
Boss,
سيدي
are you going to prepare this nice-looking champagne
هل حضرت هذه الزجاجة من الشمبانيا الجميلة الليلة
or this nice-tasting champagne?
أم هذه الزجاجة من الشمبانيا اللذيذة
You're preparing champagne?
ما هو الشمبانيا
Do you know Drizzle?
هل تعرف شي يو كبيرة؟
Ridiculous.
غريب
You're Mr. Smart?
أنت ذكي
Yes.
نعم
You are...
أنت أنت
Drizzle?
أمطار غزيرة
You're right.
أنت على حق
The risk of online dating is too high.
المخاطر كبيرة في الحب عبر الإنترنت
You liar, why did you pretend to be a sweet guy?
أنت كاذب لا تتظاهر بأنك رجل دافئ
How am I a liar?
كيف أكون كاذبة
I didn't pretend to be a sweet guy.
لا أتظاهر بأنني رجل دافئ
When we were talking,
عندما كنا نتحدث
didn't you also pretend
أنت لا تتظاهر
to be gentle?
‫تتكلم بهدوء
If I knew it was you, I wouldn't have pretended.
أعلم أنه أنت لن أتظاهر
See? You admit it.
انظر هل اعترفت
You deceived a good guy.
أنت تخدع فتى صالح
You're a good guy?
أنت فتى صالح
You're just cosplaying Black and White Impermanence.
أعتقد أنك تقلد الظلام والبيضاء
Black and White Impermanence have feelings too.
هناك مشاعر أيضًا
You deceived my feelings.
أنت تخدع مشاعري
Deceived your feelings? Bah!
تخدع مشاعرك
I'm telling you, I'll beat you
أقول لك إذا رأيتك مرة أخرى في المستقبل
every time I see you.
سأضربك مرة واحدة
Then I'll...
سأراك مرة واحدة
avoid you every time I see you.
سوف أختبئ منك مرة واحدة
Hello.
مرحباً
You're here.
أنت هنا
I still have a lot of things to do.
لا يزال لدي الكثير من الأشياء لم أكملها
Give me some time.
أعطني المزيد من الوقت
I know you haven't finished your task.
أعرف أن مهمتك لم تنته بعد
That's why I turned a blind eye
لهذا السبب تجاهلت
to your expired visa.
تجاهلك
But Xiao Jing,
لكن يا أخي
I'm a civil servant of the Time Management Bureau.
أنا موظف رسمي في مكتب إدارة الزمان والمكان
I'm not a shepherd.
أنا لا أستسلم
Look.
انظر انظر
How many times did I let you go?
كم مرة تركتك
You're going too far.
أقول لك إنك تتجاوز حدودك أكثر فأكثر
The magnetic field is getting worse.
يؤثر على المجال المغناطيسي أكثر فأكثر
I came here because I had no choice.
‫لم يكن لدي خيار آخر لذلك أتيت هذه المرة
I...
أنا
I'll try to be careful.
يجب أن تنتبه
You're an illegal time-traveler now.
أنت الآن تاجر أسود
Don't forget your mission
لا تنسي أن لديك مهمتك
and your sister.
وأختك
I think
أعتقد أنك
you're too deeply involved now.
أنت في حالة عميقة الآن
No.
لا
You can't continue to affect this place.
لا يمكنك الاستمرار في تأثير هذا المكان
No matter if it's the celestial phenomena
بغض النظر عن الظاهرة السماوية
or the people
لا يزال هناك شخص
and their fates.
و مسار مصيرهم
I don't need to remind you about the consequences.
‫لا يجب أن أذكرك العواقب‬
Bo Yan.
‫بويان‬
Do you know something?
‫هل تعرف شيئا‬
Did you know I was destined to come here early
‫هل تعرف أن مقدر لي أن آتي إلى هنا مبكرا‬
and meet her?
مقدر لي أن أقابلها
Tell me.
أخبرني
What happened
ماذا حدث
Did I affect her
هل أثرت عليها
or did she affect me?
أم تأثرت علي
Maybe
ربما
it's something that escaped from space and time.
سمكة هروب الشبكة خارج الزمان والمكان
I can't see what is going to happen
ما حدث لكما
between you two.
لا أستطيع رؤيتها
However,
لكن
you won't bring her any good result.
لن تجلب لها نتيجة جيدة
Don't forget.
لا تنسي
You are going back.
أنت الشخص الذي ستعود
If you tell me
إذا أخبرتني
you want to play with her feelings.
أنك تريد أن تلعب مشاعر هذه الفتاة
Fine.
حسنا
I have no objections.
‫لا يمكنني السيطرة على ذلك ولا مشكلة‬
But don't get yourself involved.
لكن لا تقع نفسك في ورطة
You still have one and a half months.
لديك نصف شهر
If you trigger these phenomena
إذا لم تنهي المهمة
before the mission is completed,
إذا تحركت هذه الظاهرة مرة أخرى
I'll have to take you back
فلا بد أن آخذك إلى المنزل
and make you guard the space-time rift.
حارس الباب الفارغ في ذلك الوقت
I'm going.
لنذهب
Orange.
البرتقال
She's fine.
إنها بخير
Who are you?
من أنت؟